What did you do?
Cheska!
It's Shane, isn't it?
I've already been screwed over,
and now you're making me look stupid?
What do you want from me?
- The truth!
- You can't handle it.
Liar!
It's the truth, Cisco!
I don't believe you!
You think that I cheated?
Can you accept that?
Do you even deserve my love?
Cisco…
Yes, Ms. Ana.
Their final decision is
not to proceed with the DBS.
- We're heading back to Singapore.
- What? No, no, no!
I'll talk to them. I can convince them.
I'll be there around five.
6:00 AM latest, Ms. Ana.
Dad, can I use your car, please?
Wait, I'll check if our driver is back.
No, I don't need a driver. I can manage.
It's like a seven-to-eight-hour drive.
Did you even sleep last night?
I'm fine.
Please?
Isa, can I use your car?
- Fran?
- Dad?
No.
The last time you drove,
your car was a wreck.
It was an accident!
I was not trying to kill myself!
Son.
I know how difficult it is
to move on after a relationship--
Really?
You had a hard time?
Cisco!
I'll just find my own ride.
JC.
My love!
You forgot the keys.
Oh!
My heart!
Thank you!
Sorry about that.
We're newlyweds.
Oh, right.
This is my wife, Lisa.
Cisco, meet Lisa.
Cisco? Isn't he--?
Uh…
My heart!
You left the stove on.
You should go check on it.
But I'm not cooking anything, love.
Well, cook something!
I'm hungry. Your husband is hungry.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Too bad you and Cheska missed our wedding.
You guys inspired me to find love.
The keys, JC?
Wait. Don't you want to shave?
I know you want to look like me, but
Cheska won't take you back
if you look like that.
The keys.
Remember,
I love you.
But I love my new car more.
Take care of it.
Return it with a full tank
and charged, okay?
Does it have those now?
Of course not!
You just borrowed it now.
Thanks.
All right. Just press the key,
and you'll find it.
My car is as handsome as me.
Hi, ex.
- No.
- Definitely not.
That's why it's an X.
As your ex, I say big red "X"
to whatever you're planning.
Not now. I'm in a hurry.
Exactly why I'm rushing to stop you.
Why are you doing this?
You know why.
Honestly, I don't.
Because to be honest,
you don't have the right anymore.
We're not doing this now.
Ooh. That sounded like a command.
I say we do the breakup trip.
Please go away.
Not until we do the breakup trip.
There you go again.
No!
Yes!
Cisco,
why do you keep delaying the inevitable?
So annoying!
It's been almost two years.
Let's do the breakup trip!
I'm going somewhere more important.
Look, we both need to move on.
If you do this with me, I'll shut up.
For good.
Let's do this!
Breakup trip! Breakup trip!
Breakup trip!
Mm? Why didn't you pin Mt. Polis?
That's the endpoint of our breakup trip.
We agreed to do
the breakup trip before we--
I did not agree.
I just knew you wouldn't leave me alone.
Not fair.
Shhh.
See? They're not answering.
It only means one thing.
That's the call that you should take!
Hey!
That's your mom!
She's offering you a job.
You can start over in Australia--
I don't want to be a nepo baby.
Set your pride aside. You need this.
What I need is for people to believe me.
I need them to see there is hope,
there is still a chance--
That's not what you want.
All you want is control.
You have to get your way.
If I'm right, why shouldn't I?
Some things just never change.
You're still the same pushy guy who will
do everything just to get your way.
No, I'm not.
- Who only cares about winning!
- Stop!
- You know nothing's gonna change--
- Stop being pessimistic!
I'm just being realistic!
As you should be!
So you should go to Australia and move on.
I refuse to move on!
Oh, what a line!
- You're expecting to get back--
- Stop!
You know,
for someone trying to win their ex back,
you're the grumpiest.
So gloomy. And you look like you smell.
I'm not trying to get back together.
We're still together.
Do I need to remind you
yet again how it ended?
I'd rather remember
why we should never end.
Fine.
Then tell me. Why?
Do we have to start where it began?
No.
I know what you're trying to do.
You can't fool me.
This is not a breakup trip.
I told the board
that these two will run
our integrated content lab.
They said I lost my mind.
"Your Gen Z prodigies do not know crap
about running this business,
so prepare to crash!"
We proved them wrong.
We are opening our own division!
So, boys, what do we call it?
Hmm?
Gold Minds.
It keeps the Guinto Group brand.
Gold standards.
Gold ideas. Gold minds.
I like that.
Not bad.
But for an attention economy,
we need a name that people will remember.
We're here to blow minds, guys.
We are here to keep the tradition.
The culture of excellence.
Then why make something new?
We have to disrupt the system, guys.
That's why we're here.
We will find that perfect spot
in our clients' brands.
Audience. Stories.
They have to connect!
The G Spot!
Oh my.
Kinky!
Witty.
- Guys, meet our new intern.
- Hi everyone!
She was my best student at CST.
OMG! You're the new housemate
Mr. G mentioned?
I believe we have a name!
The G Spot!
Good job, boys! Good job!
Amazing!
Congratulations.
Let me get a tumbler I can lend you.
Okay.
Yes!
G Spot!
G Spot. G Spot.
Here it is!
Uh…
Smells like rotten eggs.
More like poop!
Really?
- I smell nothing.
- Me too.
Just find me at my table.
How embarrassing.
Totally human.
Thanks.
Francisco Serrano.
Cisco.
Francisca Alegre.
Cisca?
Let's make it classier.
Cheska.
Oh.
Two of a kind!
Call me Tuks!
- That's their PR spin.
- Ugh, what a hassle.
They say his fiancée's just jealous.
- But she has proof.
- Their careers can't survive this scandal.
- Guys!
- Boss.
Dolce Bravo Ice Cream is in panic mode!
They need solutions in two hours.
Do we still push through
with Jesse and Andy's campaign?
Sir, I don't think we should
push through with this.
A celebrity's cheating scandal
won't die down in just two days.
They will ruin
the Dolce Bravo brand.
I say we still push through.
Huh?
We already have placements and hype.
If we pull out now,
the brand loses momentum.
Same strategy.
Just different faces.
What if we get the couple
who sing while cooking?
That won't work for the older market.
What if we get a solo artist?
But a big star!
- Great idea, right?
- Tina!
The whole product feature is a combination
of two ice cream flavors.
I need viable options, guys!
Come on, guys, think!
We need a love team that appeals
across generations.
A wholesome love team.
And please, with no scandals, okay?
- Boss!
- Yes?
Other boss.
I think Tina's idea could work--
I just said--
What if we get one star
who can carry two flavors?
Light and pure as vanilla
and as intense as dark chocolate.
A star that can make you feel two ways.
Both sweet and bold.
Like who?
Giuliarose.
She can do romcom. She can do drama.
That why she's called the Queen of Feels.
So you're saying,
why get two different tubs of ice cream…
If you can get them in one.
Okay!
Let's make a teaser.
- You'll stand in for Giuliarose.
- I can assist as well.
- You'll edit this.
- Yes, sir.
- What about the music?
- Same as before.
Perfect! We'll make a deck
with the proposed execution.
Then set a meeting for client approval.
Then we can shoot tomorrow.
We just need to inform Giuliarose's team.
I'm on it.
Now that's the perfect pair.
You two should be the new love team.
Hey, include us too. We're right here.
To G Spot!
Cisco!
- Keep it up!
- Thank you, Mr. G!
- Cisco, let's take a picture!
- Okay!
Okay.
- I'll go ahead.
- All right, be safe!
- Hey!
- Oh no, it's broken.
Cisco!
Take a picture with me too!
Let's take a groufie.
Yeah!
Leave Cisco alone, you guys!
- Let's go?
- Ready when you are.
Tuks!
Leaving already?
Yes. I'm hitching a ride with Shane.
Stay. I'll take you home instead.
I'll get you a drink!
No need. I have a lot to do anyway.
Thank you, though.
Let's go?
Are you giving up already?
Huh?
On the drinks, I mean. Drink more!
Cheers!
Hmmm.
Have you eaten, Cheska?
Not yet.
Come on, let's eat.
- You okay?
- Yes.
Are you really going home
to your province tonight?
Yes. I have a lot of stuff to do.
But it's so late.
Isn't it dangerous?
I'm used to it.
Just text me
when you get home, okay?
Okay. I'll just take the bus.
- I can't find my phone.
- I'm sure it's there.
Hey. Cisco! Are you okay?
Today's extra tiring.
I know. So much work!
- Cisco!
- Are you okay?
- Hey.
- Oh my goodness.
I'm okay.
Thank you, guys!
- Are you okay?
- Yes. I don't know.
I tripped over my own foot.
I have the exact same one!
Mm?
- Yes.
- This one?
No freaking way!
We really are two of a kind!
Bam!
I'll take you home.
But I'm going home to my parents'.
That's okay.
It's a three-hour drive.
Oh.
Okay.
Here they go again.
- They're fighting again!
- It's going to be a long night!
Let's sit back and
enjoy our regular show.
She's thrown the whole
kitchen at him already.
Cheska! We're about to get
to the good part!
My timing is perfect!
- Take this, you lazy idiot!
- Please, stop!
- Big bro!
- Go be with your friends!
- Take your roosters with you!
- Oh hey!
- This will take another hour, right?
- They give me work!
More or less.
Mom has more plates to throw.
Fine, we'll go--
Oh! Hey, Cisco! Come here!
Who's this?
My officemate.
Wow, he's tall.
- My name's Rafa.
- Cisco.
- We'll be right back.
- Sure, I'll message you when they're done.
- Sure you can handle it?
- Yes.
They're my bosses!
I need to get along with them.
We can't even afford rent!
Let's just go back to the province!
- This is me.
- That's too far.
You need to be separated
from your gambler friends.
It's cold there.
You and your roosters
can freeze there.
It's okay.
Don't be embarrassed.
Dude! I just have a headache.
Why would I be embarrassed?
It's normal for couples to fight.
No, it's not.
Your parents never fight?
No.
They're separated. How would they fight?
Are you serious?
It's true!
I guess I win.
Oh?
Is that a challenge?
Yes.
Okay.
My dad's been gambling since I was two.
My mom left me when I was two.
She chose Australia.
My mom has been playing dumb for 20 years.
She won't leave my dad.
My dad had a new family
in less than 20 days.
So
I no longer have a family.
Let's start a family.
You wish!
This is me.
This is us.
Good morning!
They're a couple!
You didn't tell me you were
coming out as a couple today!
So, sir, are you now moving in with us?
Maybe.
- You guys!
- Congratulations!
As of today, officially,
Cheska is regularized!
Oh my God!
- Thank you, sir!
And… congratulations!
It may not be forbidden,
but keep it professional.
- Yes, sir.
- Promise, sir.
It could get complicated and ugly.
I've seen it happen!
But who knows?
Maybe your story will end differently.
We won't have an ending, sir.
Right?
Is that a smile?
You're smiling!
I thought you didn't want
to do the breakup trip.
Guess you gave in.
You talk too much.
So you were listening to my stories?
- This is a breakup trip.
- No, it's not.
Okay, fine.
But don't hide that smile.
You were right.
It felt almost serendipitous.
Magical.
Not almost.
It really was.
I meant it when I said
we'd have no ending.
But there's no such thing.
All must come to an end.
- There you go again.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go back to the part
where you were smiling.
Where were we?
I just miss us.
The old Cheska.
Who didn't ask for much?
Who didn't need much?
Can I carry all of this in one go?
Nope. The fragile ones first.
Tuks! Are we ready?
We are!
- Let's go, let's go!
- I'll get these.
Just roll with his mood swings.
You know how artists are.
But JC is nice.
Cisco.
This is the way.
Come in!
- Let's go.
- You were right.
Told you.
Cheska! This is it!
- Tina.
- Boss! We're housemates now.
- Let me help you.
- I got it. They're fragile.
Cheska, let's switch roomies.
You can have Tina.
- Hello.
- Behave.
Hi, bro.
- Cisco.
- I'm Bonj.
Hi, Cheska.
Hi!
Should I come back tomorrow?
- Who is she?
- She's a regular.
- A regular what?
- I'll think about it.
You were like a starfish last night.
Tukie, help!
Tukie!
I can't reach it.
Beautiful.
Tukie, the curtains will fall.
No, it's fine. Keep going.
You're tall anyway.
I can't reach it.
That's why I need you.
Oh!
Come here!
You think you can escape me?
Tuks…
Not now! Later!
Come here.
Oh, you.
Are you guys sure about this?
'Cause it's a lot!
Do you regret it?
Living together?
I actually don't think regret
is the right word.
Maybe it was just
too much too soon.
Well, living together
seemed right at that time.
Practical. Convenient.
Shared expenses.
It helped us financially.
But, yeah.
Emotionally…
It cost us a lot.
You're anxious.
Am I?
Mm.
This is why I don't want to look back.
- The past?
- You're so annoying! Shh!
Just shut up!
That's so emo.
This is so annoying.
Fate is funny sometimes, huh?
♪ If you want this to end ♪
♪ Then just say so ♪
♪ If you want this to stop-- ♪
Stop! Shut up!
What if we actually broke up?
Tuks! Change your shirt
so you can convince the client.
Is that really necessary?
Of course! You're the brains
behind the campaign.
The future is orange.
"Orange" you a little excited?
Of course!
You're getting Garcia the presidency!
"Orange" you proud of me?
Great!
Let's go, Madam President!
National average for all three metrics
is 30% or lower.
Are you serious?
Are your results accurate?
Consistent across multiple runs.
In conclusion, all three taglines
scored below 50% nationwide
across all markets.
So, it still works.
Yes. For people like you
in team G Spot.
Urban, educated, high purchasing power…
Advocacy-driven.
But we agreed to target the masses.
They're the priority, remember?
Meanwhile, the strongest
opponent nationwide…
Their most effective taglines are:
"Affordable Rice,"
"Housing for All,"
and "Affordable Onions."
These taglines resonate with more people.
Even if they know it's all a lie?
Yes.
That's what sticks.
Okay. Let's change direction.
Wait, sir.
We can't just change
our strategy like that.
Our taglines are built on truth.
This shows exactly who our candidate is.
And yet it's not working.
With all due respect,
our entire campaign is built on integrity.
Long-term trust.
With all due respect,
you won't win if nobody's listening.
Can we at least test them again
before we kill the idea completely?
- Cheska.
- Mr. G?
When you go home to your province,
what do you usually hear?
Hmm…
They don't really talk about
decent public service
or the future.
Mostly, they talk about rent,
water bills, electricity bills,
fares, tuition fees,
and how they wish food was cheaper.
Even I worry if my salary
will last the month,
or if I can still send money back home.
Bingo! That's the direction I want.
But "The Future is Orange"
is good too, sir.
Enough with the orange antics.
We're working late again tonight!
- Yup!
- Not again.
You Gen Z kids think
you're the only voters--
What about us?
Let's sit here.
Are we okay?
Huh?
Yes.
Tuks…
- I'm sorry if--
- No.
You were just being honest.
Okay?
Come on. Let's eat.
"Orange" you mad?
"Orange" you a little paranoid?
"Orange" you sweet?
I love you, Tuks.
I love you more.
I love you more, more, more, more, more.
No, I love you more, more, more, more,
more, more, more, more.
When things aren't going well,
people turn to ice cream…
That's where Dolce Bravo enters.
Maybe go straight to the point, Tuks.
- Okay. Tina, kindly note please.
- Copy.
We're staying at Mom's
for one night, right?
Two nights. We'll head there
right after your presentation.
- Come on, girl!
- Hmm?
Giuliarose has a bad image now.
Why should we keep her?
We should keep her because--
Needs more vinegar!
Tukie! Tukie!
I got this.
Look at me. Hey.
Focus on the pitch, okay?
We have to prove Giuliarose to the client.
We cannot lose Dolce Bravo.
That account is ours.
We have to be present
even during the bad days--
No! That's awful!
It's awful?
No, I meant this.
I punched the holes wrong.
- It looks awful.
- Don't mind him. Continue.
Tuks…
can I really do this?
Maybe you should do the presentation?
Tuks, you can do it.
And Cheska, you were trained by the best.
You got this!
I got this.
Ice cream has always been about
more than just perfectly sweet moments.
In fact, people turn to ice cream
when things are not perfect.
When life gets messy,
stressful, and complicated.
We're an ice cream brand.
A family brand. We should stay wholesome.
Giuliarose isn't wholesome anymore.
So why are you insisting on keeping her?
We also learned that consumers
don't support Giuliarose anymore.
And you still want to keep her?
A bad girl?
But Dolce Bravo
was never just about being good.
Or for the good ones.
But it's also about comfort,
regardless if you're good or bad.
The brand sticks with her.
With us.
Not just when you're at your best
but especially when you're not.
Why is Cheska a little moody?
She's just tired from the trip.
Are you okay?
You were quiet the whole ride.
I thought I was alone.
You were pretending to sleep.
You didn't even get me a drink.
What? Is this about the pitch?
I was just trying to help.
- I didn't need your help.
- You obviously did.
If I'd needed your help,
I'd have let you know.
The client was getting agitated.
- You were taking too long to answer.
- Seriously? That was just a beat.
Can't I gather my thoughts for a second?
That's called dead air.
You cannot have dead air.
I was gonna say something.
You just cut in.
Just admit you don't trust me enough.
I wouldn't have made you lead the pitch
if I didn't trust you.
Okay. Then why did you hijack
my presentation, huh?
- I was saving you--
- I did not need saving!
I will always save you.
You're my girlfriend!
Wow. I don't even know who I'm talking to
right now, my boyfriend or my boss?
Both!
I always will care for you
as my girlfriend and my subordinate.
I want you to succeed!
With what you did,
you're the only one who succeeded.
You made me look incompetent!
Both of us will look incompetent
if I didn't save you.
Oh, so my mistake is going to
be yours, huh?!
Of course!
Command responsibility.
- I'm done!
- Me too!
- Copycat!
- Whatever! Goodbye!
Goodbye? That's it?
Did you hear that, Mr. G?
Of course! Even Sally heard it.
- Hey, I'll get the usual.
- Okay, sir.
Mr. G, who has a point between us?
Hmm.
I believe you both have a point.
And it showed in the results because…
we still got the account.
- Congratulations!
- Yay!
You want to celebrate at my place?
We're going to Mt. Polis.
You should come with us, Mr. G.
Oh no. My knees.
You can go ahead.
But leave now
if you want to catch the sea of clouds.
The sea of clouds! Thank you, Mr. G!
Stop by the rest house
on your way back, okay?
- Cheska, say hi to your parents for me!
- Okay, boss!
Did we break up?
Kind of.
But are we okay now?
Shortest breakup ever.
Let's never do that again.
Never.
That hurt even if it was just quick.
Agreed.
Never again.
Here's the pitch.
A breakup trip.
You mean like breakup sex?
No. That complicates things.
This is the opposite.
How about this?
If, only if,
one or both of us
wants to quit the relationship,
no running away.
No leaving without an explanation.
No ghosting.
No goodbye texts or DMs.
Exactly.
No quiet quitting, slow fading,
soft blocking, r-bombing,
love droughting, orbiting,
submarining, zombie-ing!
So that we don't do to each other…
Smile.
…what my parents did to me.
Okay?
Never.
So if ever we do want to end things,
we don't just walk away,
we don't just disappear.
We drive.
To?
Here, of course.
Maybe we'll catch the sea of clouds then.
There's none right now.
So, a long drive?
Let's give each other time
to make sense of our decision
and what happened to us.
No unanswered questions.
No what-ifs.
Let's say everything.
Even the painful truths?
Especially the painful truths.
We have to have a complete and honest
review about our relationship.
That's what the road trip is for.
Tuks, let's make an agreement.
We will take a breakup trip.
We'll survive through traffic,
tears,
and the truth.
Deal?
That sounds so corporate.
Let's call it a promise.
No, better than a promise.
Mm?
A covenant.
My gosh! That should've been the ending!
We should've gotten married after that.
Okay, double time.
Frame one, okay?
Let's lock the shot
before the director gets here.
Tina! Costume. Wardrobe.
Miss Giuliarose!
This is the way to makeup.
There's no need. I'm ready to shoot.
Where's the director?
He's on his way.
Let's say hi to the Dolce Bravo team.
Tuks, where are you?
Tuks, we're still on the road.
The client pitch ran overtime.
Giuliarose and the clients are here.
The traffic hasn't moved for hours.
What do you want me to do?
Can't we reschedule?
Giuliarose is flying to Paris tomorrow.
She'll be there for two months.
When is the release date?
End of this month.
Shit! This is bad!
Can you wait for me, Tuks?
We only have two hours until sunset, Tuks.
Shoot it.
No.
I'll call Shane.
No. I'd rather have you
direct this thing than Shane.
Cisco.
I don't know what to do.
I'm getting bored.
We're running out of daylight.
Tukie, just follow my storyboard.
Everything's written there.
It's going to be okay.
You can do it.
Okay?
Oh my god.
Preview!
She doesn't look happy
with the product.
Is she going through something?
- Does she have a problem?
- That's not my problem.
Giuliarose is throwing a fit again.
We've been here all day.
How many more shots to go?
Poor Cheska. How will she finish this?
Following Cisco's storyboard,
two more shots to go.
- What should we do?
- Here.
Kookai, Vince, follow me.
Stand by.
Okay, guys, I'm here!
Stay here, we're rolling.
- Which shot is this?
- Here's the storyboard.
I don't know.
- Let's see what Cheska's doing.
- You don't know?
Quiet.
Okay, let's wait.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Do you want to talk?
Be quiet. She's comforting her.
Tissue.
I'm sorry.
Roll the camera.
Cheska, here.
To make you happy.
- Oh, she's finally smiling!
- Yeah!
Oh my God.
That's what Cheska's been doing.
Now I get it.
Cheska's directing style works.
Cut!
We got it!
That's the shot!
Cheska, thank you.
I love it.
Thank you.
From now on,
I want her to always be my director.
Cheska is amazing!
Thank you.
- Best director!
- Not really.
No, really.
I'll even recommend you to my friends.
Hey, Allie!
Can we request that
Cheska direct my upcoming projects?
So Cisco won't be directing anymore?
- I don't think so.
- Cheska is really great.
I love you.
I love you more.
Hi, Grandpa!
Congrats on the
Dolce Bravo ad, Cheska!
- Thank you!
- Yes, Cheska.
You know, I never really liked Giuliarose,
but now she seems so real and relatable.
- Right?
- Exactly.
I've always had a crush on Giulia
and now I want to comfort her.
Ew. That's not what we're talking about!
It was so good,
even my friends shared the ad.
You know, Cheska,
I told my friends you directed it,
and they're so excited
to see your future work.
Thank you, but the birthday boy
should get all the credit.
- Really?
- That was his idea.
- Wow!
- I just executed it.
That's nice, Cisco.
Good job, son.
How long will you be doing that, Cisco?
Grandpa?
You've been at it for a while now.
Cheska already beat you to a big hit.
Dad, Cisco's done a lot already--
Small,
inconsequential stuff.
Not as viral as Cheska's.
Perhaps
you need to reconsider
your career plans, Cisco.
- Pa.
- Look.
We need a Marketing and Advertising Head
in the Logistics Division.
Why don't you join us, Cisco?
Grandpa, I have no plans
of entering the family business.
That's what your papa said too.
Until reality hit him.
Not everyone can make
their passion their career.
What do you want, son?
Do you want to grow old
with nothing to show for?
You might get left behind.
Even by your siblings.
You are being silly, Grandpa.
Look, what I'm saying is,
in a creative industry,
passion is not enough.
Hell, hard work is not enough.
What you need is solid talent.
If you're just middling,
or at best mediocre,
you'll end up like your mother.
A has-been.
Dad, let's just eat.
The food is good.
Let's just enjoy it.
Right.
We have to break through
the social media space.
Sir, the clients are here.
Let's go.
I heard Sir Shane is resigning.
Girl, no! He just got transferred
to the other wing.
Why?
He's now a junior member of the board
as the new head of G Spot.
Wow! He's a big boss now.
We're presenting the brand as aspirational
and still accessible!
So the tone is confident.
Slightly irreverent.
But that's not for our target market.
But that's the type of tone you need.
We need to break through
the social media space.
Your brand's already
falling behind!
You know why?
You present yourself as super safe.
So forgettable.
Do you want our business or not?
Do you want me or not?
Because we're telling you
what you need to hear,
not what you want to hear.
It's your choice.
Rommel, can you give Cisco and I a second?
We just have an urgent client concern
for another brand.
Cheska, can you continue…
…presenting the campaign to Mr. Reyes?
Yes, Mr. G.
- What was that?
- Sir, you have to understand.
- I was just being honest with them.
- No, you were being rude!
That's my way of making sure
that there's a strategy in place--
You don't call insulting
your clients strategy!
Strategy does not work
if they don't want to work with you.
Take a break.
Sir, I'm not taking a break.
This is my account.
No!
Take a break.
We will handle this from here.
- Great!
- Nice!
Thank you for the trust.
Well, we love Cheska's vision
for the company.
That's why we're sticking with you.
And we promise to deliver
within the timeframe.
Great!
But we want Cheska to lead the campaign.
Right, Cheska?
Of course!
Cheska it is.
- Thank you, Cheska.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
- Sir, I'll just accompany them downstairs.
- All right, see you!
As the new head of G Spot,
Shane will handle all planning, budgeting,
and staffing decisions,
while you can focus on
developing venture accounts.
Smaller emerging brands
open to partnership models.
Cheska will now be
reporting directly to Shane.
She'll be
on developmental assignment.
And I'll be training her on account
and strategic management.
You'll still be doing local accounts,
but we're really positioning her
to bring in international clients.
Why?
I can bring in international clients.
Oh really?
You've always had contact
with an international account,
but why haven't you offered
our services to them?
We found out from Cheska
that your stepdad
is the CEO of Taylor-Smith Australia.
You want me to pull the nepo baby card?
But this is business.
Easy for you to say.
Cisco, we all want what's best
for the company.
For G Spot!
For us to stay competitive.
- And adapt to a very volatile--
- Stay competitive?
Adapting?
While keeping me on the sidelines?
Sir, I built this division.
I even named it!
And now I'm being asked to chase startups
while someone else heads this division
and my subordinate
trains to take over my job!
We are just restructuring.
Realigning roles--
You're pushing me away.
You don't want me here.
That's not what we're saying.
It's okay.
I get it.
I'm out.
The logo is okay.
- We just need to make it bolder.
- Right.
Hey! What do you mean bold?
I've changed my mind!
I'm pulling my money out!
- Hey, don't, JC!
- Please don't!
How about colors?
Should we do all black?
Why not?
As long as it's timeless.
Do you want to try a 3D printer?
- I'll add some bevel and texture.
- Sounds great!
Hello.
- Tuks?
- There she is!
Finally!
You're home!
Shawn, Tuks, our graphic designer.
Mookie's friend.
And my buddy from college.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So nice to finally meet you.
I'm the old Cheska.
Did you guys smooch too?
JC!
Of course not!
I was his producer
in all our college projects.
I heard you're his new Mookie.
Female version, of course.
Upgraded version actually!
Mookie will make sure the operations
are set so we can launch soon.
Launch?
What launch, Tuks?
That's the surprise, Tuks!
JC finally said yes!
He's going to be one of our investors.
I sold my kidneys so I could invest.
You're the best, JC!
Bonj is also investing!
- That's why he was asking me--
- Woo!
Cisco!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm okay! Don't worry, guys.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
You've had a bit too much to drink, Cisco.
Spill on aisle three.
You're good, you're good.
As I was saying, Tuks,
since I'm no longer a corporate slave,
why do we need bosses
if we can be our own boss?
Huh?
I mean, since we always
work best together,
why do it for someone else
if we can do it for ourselves?
Together?
You and me!
Let's start our own production house!
And the best part?
Cisco already has a name.
Tuks! CXC!
Cisco and Cheska!
It's great, right?
Not bad.
You'll join me here, won't you?
Right?
There's no CXC without Cheska.
Only if you want to, of course.
We only need
one last big investor.
Where are we going
to find another investor?
- Desperate times, desperate measures.
- Why not your dad?
Your grandpa?
Can't they invest?
Ches…
Are you really resigning?
Dad.
I already agreed to invest.
Let us help Cisco.
Your grandson rarely asks for our help.
Why are you the one begging?
Is your son too arrogant to beg?
Please, Grandpa.
Please what?
Help me build my business.
I need your help.
Is Cheska part of this?
Yes.
She is?
She believes in this?
Enough to leave Guinto Group?
She will oversee operations
and client management.
Good.
Kiko, call Albert.
Tell him to prepare a check for Cisco.
Yes, Dad.
Thank you, Grandpa.
I will not let you down.
I promise.
Thank you, Grandpa.
Thank you.
Wow.
- It's spacious!
- It's perfect.
- Cool, isn't it?
- Looks even better in person.
This can be our statement wall.
We can have our centerpiece over here.
I can paint it!
How much?
Do it for free.
Part of your investment.
- For free?
- Mooks!
- Content corner, what do you think?
- Editing bays here would be better.
- The content corner can be there instead.
- What do you think, Shawn?
- Yeah!
- This spot has better lighting.
Wow! What a glow-up!
She's so ready to be a CEO!
You look…
different.
I just…
needed a change.
That's exactly what you're gonna get!
Welcome to our new content playground!
We'll provide groundbreaking
content creation.
What do you think?
Mookie! Did you get our equipment already?
We still need more.
We'll secure more
once we receive the funding.
I'll get a check from Grandpa later.
- So we can prepare for the soft launch!
- Cisco--
- Nice!
- Cisco.
Cisco.
Can we talk?
Yes. Later.
You know, I'm excited to see
the Cisco and Cheska chemistry!
Oh, you boys have not seen
our chemistry together.
We make magic.
- For sure.
- They're like chemists, actually!
Cisco!
I'm not resigning.
I'm sorry.
I'm not joining you.
Hey!
Cisco!
Long time, no see.
I like your new hair.
I need gas.
Oh.
That's been out of business
for a while now.
Even the eatery is closing down soon.
Really?
Yup, it went bankrupt.
See?
Even this place is trying
to move on from you.
Everything must end.
Why can't you accept that?
Everyone has moved on except you.
I need to say sorry to you.
I still need to make it up to you.
Cisco, I'm not coming back!
Don't say that.
Don't say that!
Why don't you believe me?
Because the thought of you coming back
is the only thing keeping me alive!
Because if it's just me, I'm done.
I hate myself for being alive!
If my driver answers.
- He doesn't speak Japanese.
- I told you so.
Let's just bring your car, Shane.
Let's eat already because I'm so hungry!
- Ma'am, your bag.
- Thanks, Nabi!
- Let me--
- I got it.
Cisco, are you joining us for dinner?
Huh?
Tuks, I messaged you…
I didn't receive anything.
It's okay, Cheska.
We can have dinner some other time.
- Sorry, Mr. G.
- It's okay.
Cisco.
Nice seeing you again, Cisco.
Oh, Cheska, congrats again.
You deserve it.
They gave you my job.
Damn it!
They gave you my position.
You know this is their strategy, right?
For the upcoming client pitch.
You against me?
What a smart move, huh?
They waited for me to leave
before they promoted you.
It's probably because Shane likes you.
Now that's foul.
Am I wrong?
He's always had a thing for you.
But I got you.
Can't admit that?
Just admit this then.
That fucking promotion is the only reason
why you won't join me in CXC.
You used your family as an excuse!
You know my family is in a lot of debt--
Exactly! CXC would have
been the best option!
- For your financial needs!
- My brother is having a kid!
- This is your own company--
- My parents rely on me.
You could earn more here!
In the future!
But right now,
I need a stable job, Cisco--
Just tell me you don't trust me, Cheska.
- What?
- You don't trust me.
You don't trust that I can succeed.
That this company will make money.
- Cisco, I believe in you--
- Really?
That I can make this work?
- That I can provide for you, Cheska?
- Cisco, it's not about trust!
It's about responsibility!
So now I'm irresponsible? Me?!
It's about my, my, responsibilities!
It's easy for you to quit
and start your own business
because no one is relying on you!
You can ask for help from your family.
My life is different from yours.
Then you shouldn't have led me on!
Led you on?
I thought we were building
CXC together, Cheska!
I thought you were on my side.
I am!
But that doesn't mean
I'll do everything you say!
So you're not leaving Mr. G?
I can't right now.
Right now?
Or ever?
So you'll only join me
once the business is successful?
Once I've proven myself?
I thought I didn't have to
prove myself to you.
What are you doing?
I just hope you realize
what this means, Cheska.
You were promoted
because they want to pit you against me.
This has been Mr. G
and Shane's plan all along.
I hope you know.
But fine.
Let's keep this professional.
I'll see you at the pitch.
Here's the thing you asked me to buy.
- Shawn?
- Yes?
- Why is it so small?
- It's all they had.
Start small!
Whatever idea we will pitch
to Nuevas Alturas,
they can't just imagine it.
We have to have proof!
Guys!
It needs to be shot
and edited already for our tech.
- Do you understand what he's saying?
- Nope.
We need a live demo.
The initial market scan said
condo ownership is a low priority.
There's also an emotional barrier.
They don't see the Nuevas Alturas condo
as something they deserve.
And we deserve a confident
diva queen leader!
Drink medicine if you have a headache.
Otherwise, enough being
a martyr girlfriend.
Mm?
Go on. Have a reset.
G?
Spot.
Let's go!
G Spot will make the same promises we can.
Agility.
Affordability.
They'll use the credentials
of Guinto Group.
So we leverage with conviction,
not just credentials.
Oh my! We're convicted!
There's no escape!
We're just investors here, right?
Guys, guys!
G Spot will keep things simple.
We'll make simple look small.
Other agencies will go for grand ideas
to match the high-end image of the client.
G Spot will go simple.
But not simplistic.
As a young person,
what does it mean
when you have your own condo?
It means I'm making money!
- You're not young!
- It means you're successful!
Yes, and…?
Your own world.
- Control?
- Yes.
Independence.
Having your own place
means all your hard work has paid off.
It's your reward for being the best.
Guys! Mookie.
Food from Cheska.
Perfect! My kidney is sick
of all the junk food.
Break time?
- Want some?
- No, thanks.
High-rise.
As you rise higher above everyone else.
Thoughts?
I don't like high-rise buildings
because it's lonely at the top.
Meaning?
Oh, rice porridge!
Hi, rice!
That's why it's important
that we're able to make choices
that we can stand by and commit to.
Choices that will help us grow
and change for the better.
CISCO DIDN'T EAT.
I told you so.
And if we get that right,
the condo sells itself!
And when you own
a Nuevas Alturas condominium,
you can finally say to the world,
"I've made it."
Where you can finally be yourself and say,
"I'm home."
You're ready!
Let's do this!
Cheers, guys!
- Cheers!
They aren't home yet?
They work harder than we do.
Bonj!
I miss my bed!
- Come home already, I miss you!
- I haven't slept yet.
Bonj, how's Cisco?
Bonj! Confidentiality.
- All right, bye.
- That's why we're here!
Your boyfriend is too competitive.
All right, guys.
Let's go through the pitch
one more time. C'mon.
C, aren't we going home yet?
I already flipped my underwear.
And my girlfriend's looking for me.
And I need to look for a girlfriend.
What about you?
Don't you miss your girlfriend?
So what do you think?
Um, yes, I agree, sir.
Actually, it would be best if we--
We might be up next.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
I think we're good to go.
Remember, confident
but not aggressive, okay?
Yes.
You look great.
You too.
This won't break us.
I really meant what I said.
Then why did you do what you did?
Guys, shouldn't there be an update
if we got the client or not?
Followed up, but still no reply.
Maybe they just can't choose.
Cheska is really good after all.
JC…
Ah, but Cisco is better, of course!
Dad.
We'll get this account.
We better.
If we want to propel CXC forward,
we need a big client.
- Maybe we should start--
- Grandpa!
Dad!
Guys, my grandfather.
Our major investor, as you all know.
And my dad.
- This is my team, Grandpa.
- Hi, sir!
- Where's Cheska?
- Sir, Cheska is not part of our team.
It's an all-boys team.
I mean, four-and-a-half boys.
What happened?
Uh…
Cheska decided to stay
with the Guinto Group,
but we will make sure that--
I agreed to invest in this company
because of Cheska.
We will manage perfectly without Cheska.
Your investment will not
go to waste, Grandpa.
I promise you.
Bro. Cisco.
Excuse me.
What?
Your son is full of himself.
He's treading on unfamiliar ground
and has the stupidity
to surround himself with these idiots.
We just got our first client.
I did it without Cheska.
We beat her.
You will see that you are
mistaken, Grandpa.
We'll see.
Did you hear that?
Sounds like we're getting avocados!
Congrats to CXC!
- CXC minus Cheska!
- Minus Cisco too!
Where is he anyway?
Did he go with Mookie?
He was just here!
Did he join Mookie to pick up Kizzy?
He's not there.
Oh, there he is!
Are you still working?!
- We should be celebrating already!
- Enough of that!
Ooh! There's Cheska!
Look!
That's cute.
Aw!
Bro!
Congratulations, bro!
- JC!
- Yes?
You better stop him!
They just had a big fight, and now this?
- They'll both get whiplash!
- Why would I stop him?
Instead of playing house,
it's better they finally get married!
That way, they'll be more blessed.
So I support this!
But!
What if Cheska rejects him?
Um…
But what if she doesn't?
That's why he's going to pop her
the question, isn't he?
You know,
as a matter of fact,
they're my inspiration and reason
as to why my cold heart
has finally melted.
Looks like I'll be
the next to find love.
- Are you insane?
- Ouch!
We have bigger problems right now!
My goodness!
You really want to do this now?
There's no better time than now.
Double celebration!
Cheers!
Well, hurry up!
- Go to her already!
- That's right.
- Why are you still here?
- Don't pressure him!
Scooch over!
Call her already so she knows!
Ms. Cheska,
Mr. G is calling you to his office.
Okay.
Tuks!
Tuks, are you done with work?
Oh yes.
Mr. G just wants to meet.
Why?
Ah…
To celebrate.
I'm going to break the news
before Mr. G does.
CXC won the pitch!
Congratulations, Tuks!
I'm sorry.
You're not mad, are you?
No.
You deserve it.
Thank you.
So…
Can I ask you out to dinner tonight?
So we can celebrate.
And… talk?
Yes, Tuks. See you.
Yes!
Okay! Marble and Grill tonight?
I'll see you then.
Okay, Tuks.
Okay, perfect.
I love you, Tukie.
I love you more.
I love you more, more, more. Bye-bye!
My prostate can't handle all this emotion!
Hey, Cisco!
From CXC
to C heart C!
Cisco, you should shower first!
Whoo! We can finally celebrate!
It's them until the end!
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Sorry about them.
Before you, Cheska,
I was willing to spend
the rest of my life alone.
But then you came and I…
Wine, sir?
Sorry, hold on.
You'd think this was a pitch.
Cisco, just relax!
You're right. Sorry.
Mookie!
Hello, Cisco.
Have you checked your email?
Huh? What email?
The one from…
They just sent it now?
All right, I'll check it now.
Hi, Tuks!
Tukie, my head hurts again--
You knew about this?
About what?
"Different direction
with a different agency
to fit our brand best."
You're the different agency?
Fuck.
Cisco, can we talk at home--
Plot twist!
Seems rigged, huh?
Bill, please.
I can pay.
So what happened?
The client was mine, but now they're not.
What did you guys do?
What did you do that
changed the client's mind?
Was it Shane's doing? Or Mr. G's?
Cheska!
Did you enjoy it?
You're happy you beat me, aren't you?
It's Shane, isn't it?
That asshole has been setting me up
for failure since day one!
That's not true.
So now you're siding with them?
Cheska, they forced me out of G Spot!
Was that not enough for them?
They're kicking me while I'm down,
and you're just letting them.
Talk to me!
I've already been screwed over,
and now you're making me look stupid?
Don't you feel bad?
Aren't you guilty?
What do you want from me?
- The truth!
- You can't handle it.
What do you mean?
Why can't I handle the truth?
Cheska! You think
I can't handle the truth?
- You guys stole the client from me!
- We didn't steal anything!
- You took that account from me!
- I gave it up for you!
They chose me, not you!
Liar!
It's the truth, Cisco!
I won that account!
But I made up
this bullshit excuse to the client
so it would go to you instead.
I practically sabotaged my career
just so you would win.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe you!
Wow.
I'm not sure which is more insulting.
That you think that I cheated,
or that you'd rather
believe that I cheated
than accept that I won that account
because I am just as good as you!
Or maybe even better!
Are you always going to be like this
whenever I beat you?
If I'm the one winning,
can you be happy for me?
If I outgrow you,
can you accept that?
When I do better than you or outdo you…
can you still love me?
You want to be the only winner.
You want to be the only one at the top.
But how about me?
You just want me to clap for you.
Is this the only version of us
that works for you?
All my love, all my sacrifices,
all that?
For this?
For you?
Now I'm wondering…
do you even deserve my love?
Do you even love me?
Cisco…
Cheska!
Cisco, Mela is really
against the DBS treatment.
- We don't--
- Give me that.
Cisco.
Our daughter has been in a coma
for two years now.
We're thankful for all your financial help
and the sacrifices you've made
ever since Cheska had the aneurysm.
We know you mean well
and only want the best for Cheska.
But that experimental DBS treatment
that you keep bringing up…
They're just going
to open her head up again!
She almost died last time!
What if she doesn't make it this time?
I won't risk my daughter's life!
So whatever it is
you're thinking of trying, stop!
But please--
Is this about the DBS?
Cheska's parents told me that
they've finally made a decision.
Why are you still forcing it?
I don't want to regret anything.
Mr. G, you know us.
You know how much I loved her.
Yes.
And I saw how much she loved you too.
More than you probably ever know.
I will tell you some things
that will hurt.
But you need to hear them.
You almost declined your promotion
because you were too afraid
to hurt his feelings.
And now you let go of this big
of an account and opportunity?
May I remind you, Cheska,
this is for the company.
Not just for you
and definitely not for Cisco.
Mr. G, I'm just worried
I won't handle the load--
I know you.
If you really wanted it,
nothing would stop you.
I know what it's like
to dim your own light
to let your partner shine.
To make yourself smaller.
So that you could make
the person that you love
feel like… he's enough.
To completely lose yourself
just to continue loving him.
Cheska, I know
how difficult this is for you,
but the company also needs this account.
We deserve this win.
You deserve this win.
You worked so hard for this.
And so did the rest of your team.
And I will get this account back,
whether you approve of it or not.
Mr. G.
Is it okay if we outsource
one execution to their team?
Let Cisco be the director.
He's still the best.
Unbelievable.
Okay, fine.
Thank you, Mr. G.
I'm sorry.
She was selfless.
But I guess
she never got to tell you that.
Even that final win?
Something that she can claim
solely as her own?
She was willing to share that with you.
That's how much she loved you.
I don't deserve her.
I know you love her too.
I never doubted that.
But this thing that you're doing,
forcing Cheska to wake up?
Ask yourself.
Who are you really doing it for?
If Cheska lives, then she lives.
And if she does,
is this the version of Cisco
that you want her to wake up to?
If you really want to apologize to her,
then be the man that she loved
and she believed that you could be.
I was worried.
Hi, Tuks.
It's me again.
Not to pressure you to come back already,
but… to promise that
I will be a better man.
A man truly worthy of your love.
I'm sorry, Tuks.
I hope you can forgive me.
I'm sorry for…
Not just what I said and what I did
the last time we were together.
I'm sorry for all the times that
I didn't treat you right.
For all the times that I hurt you.
For the times that I was… selfish.
You had to make yourself smaller
just so I could feel loved by you.
I'm sorry I didn't see that before, Tuks.
I'm sorry I forgot that you loved me.
I'm sorry I forgot that I loved you.
I will keep on waiting for you.
I love you.
I love you more.
More and more and more and more.
Thank you.